gothelist.com 2016-06-26

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                    PRIVACY POLICY
The List FZ LLC ("The List," "we," "our," or "us") is committed to respecting and
protecting your privacy.            This Privacy Policy applies to the “The List: Website
http://www.gothelist.com (“Website/(s)”) and our concierge services (our “Service/(s)”), and describes
how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered from/about you and all third parties on our
Website. By using our Website and Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy
Policy and our Terms of Use. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the
meaning given to them in our Terms of Use.
1.      COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
1.1     Information you provide to us directly. The List collects personally identifiable information
        when you interact with us, such as when you engage with us, contact us, use the Website and /
        or the Services. The personal information we collect may include your name, mobile number,
        mailing address, email address, and any other information necessary to fulfill your request.
1.2     You should feel free to decline to provide any information that we request, however, please
        note that in doing so, it may make it difficult for The List to fulfill your request or advertise
        your product. We use the information that we collect to provide the products or services that
        you may search or request, to improve and customize our Service, and to contact you about
        special promotions and new products.
1.3     Information we collect from Third Parties. We may collect information about you from the
        parties and services that we engage to provide your requests. We may also collect information
        about you from third party services and from publicly available sources. For example, we may
        receive information about you when you interact with our site through various social media,
        for example, by liking us on Facebook or following us on Twitter or by logging in to our
        Service through Facebook, Twitter or any other third party login. The data we receive is
        dependent upon your privacy settings with the respective social network. You should always
        review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services
        before linking or connecting them to our website.
2.      USAGE OF COOKIES AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
2.1     We may automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our Website
        or use our Service. For instance, when you visit our Website, we may send one or more
        cookies—a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters—to your computer
        that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us enhance your navigation through the Website.
        A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use our Website (e.g., the
        products you view, the links you click, how frequently you access our Website, and other
        actions you take on our website), and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time.
        We may collect log file information about your browser each time you access the Service. Log
        file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet
        Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, information about your device, referring / exit pages
        and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on our website, domain names,
        landing pages, products viewed, pages viewed, and other such information. The information
        allows for more accurate reporting, user specified product recommendation and improvement
        of our Website and Services.

2.2   We may use an email delivery, various third party marketing tools and modules to send emails
      and other marketing related activities. Pixel tags and cookies are used in those email
      messages and at our Website to help us measure the effectiveness of our marketing and how
      visitors use our site. Pixel tags (sometimes also called "clear GIFs") are small graphic files,
      invisible to the human eye, which allow websites or other online services to track users. The
      List and our third-party advertising company use pixel tags in HTML-enabled email to track
      whether (and when) the recipient opened the message.
2.3   We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure
      traffic and usage- product trends for our website. These tools collect information sent by your
      browser, including the product pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other
      information that assists us in analyzing and improving our website.
2.4   We may use the data collected through cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and
      pixel tags to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it the next time
      you use our Service; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information, including
      advertising; (c) provide and monitor the effectiveness of our website and our email
      communications; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage,
      and demographic patterns on our website; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; and (f)
      otherwise to plan for and enhance our website. The information we collect through these
      tracking technologies may be linked to the Personal Information you have chosen to share
      with us when you register.
3.    THIRD PARTY TRACKING AND ONLINE ADVERTISING
3.1   We permit third party online advertising networks to collect information about your use of our
      Website over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests
      on our Website as well as on other websites or services. Typically, the information is collected
      through cookies or similar tracking technologies. You may "opt out" of the collection of any
      information through cookies or other tracking technology by managing the preferences or
      settings on your browser or mobile device. However, if you decide not to accept our cookies,
      your ability to use some features on our site may be impaired. Please refer to your browser's or
      mobile device's technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies,
      and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and
      related technologies and how you may opt-out of some of this tracking, you may wish to
      visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org and/or the Network Advertising Initiative's online
      resources, at http://www.networkadvertising.org). We are not able to respond to Do Not Track
      signals sent by your browser at this time. Depending on your mobile device, you may not be
      able to control tracking technologies through settings. If you have any questions about opting
      out of the collection of cookies and other tracking/recording tools, you can contact us directly
      at support@gothelist.com
4.    DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
4.1   We may share your personal information in the instances described below. For further
      information on your preferences regarding your information, see the "Your Information
      preferences" section below.
We may share your personal information with:
    o  Our representatives in order to perform your requested service.
    o Third-party vendors and other service providers as needed to fulfil your request, such as retail
      merchants, dealers, agents, and other brand related companies.;
    o Third-party vendors and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, as
      necessary, to carry out their work for us, which may include identifying and serving targeted

      advertisements, billing, payment processing, hosting, and record-keeping services. The List
      uses Checkout.com to process payments and does not store your payment information or
      process payments. However, your information, including payment information, may be stored
      by third parties that transmit or process this data on our behalf. This Privacy Policy does not
      govern the data practices of our third party service providers.
    o Other companies whose products or services may be of interest to you;
    o Other parties in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of all or a
      portion of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or
      acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event
      of bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings; and
    o Third parties as required by law or subpoena or, if we reasonably believe that such action is
      necessary, to (a) comply with any applicable law or competent authority, law and/ or at the
      reasonable requests of any applicable law enforcement or regulatory authority; (b) to enforce
      our Terms of Use [link] or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to
      exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of The List, our Users, or others.
5.     SETTING YOUR COMMUNICATION PREFERENCES
5.1   You can stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the
      "unsubscribe link" provided in such communications. We make every effort to promptly
      process all unsubscribe requests. You may not opt out of Service-related communications
      (e.g., information about your orders, changes/updates to our products or features of the
      Service, technical and security notices). If you want to opt-out of having your information
      shared with third parties for marketing purposes, you may contact us directly at
      support@gothelist.com or through our support form on our Website
6.     STORAGE AND PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
6.1   Your information collected through our Website or through any other communication channel
      (e.g. phone or email) may be stored and processed in the United Arab Emirates or any other
      country in which The List or its subsidiaries, affiliates, group companies or service providers
      maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws
      governing data collection and use that may differ from UAE law, please note that we may
      transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does
      not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you hereby consent to the
      transfer of information to the United Arab Emirates or any other country in which The List or
      its parent, subsidiaries, group companies, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and
      the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
6.2   The List cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable
      physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of
      all information collected through our Website and Service. However, no security system is
      impenetrable and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%. In the event that any
      information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, The List will
      take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and, where appropriate, notify those
      individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in
      accordance with any applicable laws and regulations. If you lose or lose control of your
      password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and you may be
      subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been
      compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify The List and change your
      password immediately - we cannot be held liable in any way, either directly / indirectly for
      any actions that may be taken following your password being compromised in any way
      whatsoever.

7.       THIRD PARTIES
7.1     Our Website may integrate with or contain links to other third party sites and services. We are
        not responsible for the practices employed by third party websites or services embedded in,
        linked to, or linked from our Website and your interactions with any third-party website or
        service are subject to that third party's own rules and policies.
7.2     Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only
        the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to
        others, whether they are buyers or sellers on our Site or other sites throughout the internet,
        different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them.
        The List does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the
        privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions
        before you disclose your personal information to others.
8.      MODIFYING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION
8.1     If you want to modify, change or delete any of your information you can set your preferences
        under your account preferences on our Website. In case of any other questions about
        reviewing, modifying or deleting your information, you can contact us directly
        at support@gothelist.com or through our support form on our Website. The List may retain
        your information for a reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes.
9.      PRIVACY AND CHANGE OF CONTROL
9.1     In the event The List goes through a business transition, such as a merger, reorganization,
        financing, change of control, and / or acquisition and /or sale of all or a portion of our
        business, we may transfer your personal information as part of the transaction.
10.     CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
10.1    By using our Service, you consent to the collection, use and storage of your information by us
        in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to make changes to this
        Privacy Policy from time to time. If this Privacy Policy changes in any way, we will place an
        updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always kept
        up to date and aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what
        circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. It is your responsibility to read and
        understand our Privacy Policy and any updates with respect to the same.
If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy or our Website, you can send us
an email at support@gothelist.com or through our support form on our Website.
